sandiegoreader.com 2007-12-26

# Privacy Policy for San Diego Reader Online | www.sdreader.com

Our Privacy Policy

San Diego Reader respects your privacy. Here's our privacy policy for this site: 

**Personally Identifiable Information**   
We do track how our visitors use this site so that we can see what people like and don't like. We also analyze and aggregate information about use patterns and share the aggregated data with our advertisers (for example, we keep track of how many users see and click on particular advertisements). We may also collect personal information about you via registration for contests, surveys and online ad submission. We will not, however, release your name, e-mail address or any other personal information to anyone else outside San Diego Reader unless we have your consent or there is an emergency involving personal danger. **This means that we will not provide our advertisers or anyone else outside San Diego Reader with any information specific to you unless we have your consent.** The only San Diego Reader employees or consultants allowed access to personal information about you are those who need to have access. Any employee or consultant who violates our privacy and security policies is subject to disciplinary action, including possible termination or prosecution. 

**Cookies**   
"Cookies" are small text files that allow Web sites to store and retrieve information about you from your computer system. San Diego Reader does serve cookies to track individual site usage for later aggregation. But we do not use cookies in order to retrieve any information from your computer other than information originally sent in a San Diego Reader cookie, such as a user code. We have no control over whether and how our advertisers use cookies **that originate from their website**. 

**Children**   
San Diego Reader does not orient this site toward children or target them as an audience, nor does it screen them from using the site. Some of the material on this site is for mature audiences, and parents and guardians should take responsibility for monitoring their children's use. San Diego Reader does not collect or distribute information indicating whether a user is a child. 

**Links to Other Sites**   
This site provides links and pointers to Web sites maintained by other organizations. San Diego Reader provides these links as a convenience to users, but it does not operate, control or endorse such sites. San Diego Reader also disclaims any responsibility for the information on those sites and any products or services offered there, and cannot vouch for the privacy policies of such sites. San Diego Reader does not make any warranties or representations that any linked sites (or even this site) will function without error or interruption, that defects will be corrected, or that the sites and their servers are free of viruses and other problems that can harm your computer. 

**Policy Changes**   
This privacy policy is effective as of December 20, 2000. We may need to change it from time to time as technology and the nature of the Web keep evolving. We will post any changes to this policy as soon as they go into effect. 

**More Questions?**   
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, e-mail them to [_privacy@sdreader.com_](mailto:privacy@sdreader.com), and be sure to indicate the nature of your question or concern.
